<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:a10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel xmlns:os="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/">
    <title>contract mid-level remote Software Engineering jobs - Stack Overflow</title>
    <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs</link>
    <description>contract mid-level remote Software Engineering jobs - Stack Overflow</description>
    <image>
      <url>http://cdn.sstatic.net/Sites/stackoverflow/img/favicon.ico?v=4f32ecc8f43d</url>
      <title>contract mid-level remote Software Engineering jobs - Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs</link>
    </image>
    <os:totalResults>11</os:totalResults>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">152285</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/152285/ruby-developer-ecommerce-n-or-s-america-purepoint?a=P4rtZQSHAty</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Purepoint</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>ruby-on-rails</category>
      <category>ruby</category>
      <category>postgresql</category>
      <title>Ruby Developer Ecommerce N. or S. America at Purepoint () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>This is a fake description</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 16:10:13 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-22T16:10:13Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">141116</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/141116/expert-technical-interviewer-freelance-karat?a=LkcSbeLCa0o</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Karat</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>technical-interviewing</category>
      <category>data-structures</category>
      <category>algorithm</category>
      <category>java</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <title>Expert Technical Interviewer (Freelance) at Karat () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join our elite community of Expert Technical Interviewers.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karat&amp;rsquo;s Expert Interviewers are recognized and rewarded for doing a first-class job as top assessors of technical talent. Every interviewer in the network is an accomplished engineer. &amp;nbsp;Our interviewers include development managers from big-tech companies, start-up engineers and freelancers covering the full technology stack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible, high impact work that is compensated at highly competitive rates.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an Expert Interviewer, you will be compensated at highly competitive rates for your interviewing expertise. &amp;nbsp;The time commitment is flexible---many of our interviews happen on nights and weekends. Some experts do 5 interviews/week while others do over 25 interviews/week. &amp;nbsp;You can work from anywhere, anytime. &amp;nbsp;You will sharpen your interviewing skills and transform the interviewing experience for every candidate and company.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 15:30:49 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-23T15:30:49Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">150809</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/150809/senior-developer-oddball?a=OzKGxen5En6</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Oddball</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>ruby</category>
      <category>ruby-on-rails</category>
      <category>reactjs</category>
      <category>elixir</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <title>Senior Developer at Oddball (Culver City, CA) (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced developer to help build web and mobile apps using Rails, Elixir, React, and React Native. As an early hire on a small team, you'll have a huge stake in what we build and how we work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our engineering team is small, distributed, and largely asynchronous. We value a calm, collected environment where you can focus on doing great work. Aside from a couple of weekly check-ins or project updates, you'll be able to work interruption-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can expect top-of-the-market pay, flexible hours, and a balanced 40-hour work week. We are a mixed remote and in office team, you're welcome to work out of our sunny Los Angeles office as much as you'd like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;4+ years experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You consider yourself an expert with Ruby and JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve worked with React and Elixir, or are excited about learning them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your code is a pleasure for other engineers to read and understand easily&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can speak and write in terms that non-developers can understand clearly, whether it be in a conference call, blog post or support email&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 18:38:27 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-07T18:38:27Z</a10:updated>
      <location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Culver City, CA</location>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">135079</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/135079/full-stack-developer-product-crafter-fight-for-the-future?a=JiGdVX8sI5q</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Fight for the Future</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>user-experience</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>css</category>
      <title>FULL STACK DEVELOPER, PRODUCT-CRAFTER, TROUBLEMAKER FOR A BETTER WORLD at Fight for the Future () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A-Teams Technical Co-founder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FULL STACK DEVELOPER, PRODUCT-CRAFTER, TROUBLEMAKER FOR A BETTER WORLD.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is a small Internet freedom activism team with big victories to its credit, such as organizing the protests that defeated SOPA/PIPA, and winning net neutrality rules in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our new initiative &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/ateams/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;A-Teams&lt;/a&gt; aims to create new, two-person teams that can achieve surprising political wins in the issue area of their choice, by combining political strategy and Internet savvy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are seeking the founding technical leader for one such &amp;ldquo;A-Team.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should be supremely comfortable making and launching novel and creative additions to people&amp;rsquo;s online life, whether for web, mobile, or walled gardens like Facebook. You should love the rush of launching something on a whim, and seeing it blow up in places like Product Hunt, HN, or reddit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should also have strong political attitudes about power, freedom, fairness, or caring for others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will work alongside a similarly high-functioning and creative person with concrete experience shifting political reality, e.g. a former Congressional staffer, political campaigner, or lobbyist. We&amp;rsquo;ll work with you both to develop and execute plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU'LL DO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make a lot of awesome responsive websites, quickly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creatively use tech to mobilize people around specific political objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make a lot of simple, novel MVPs to support these plans.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Self QA and polish until they&amp;rsquo;re good enough, launch and fix issues on the fly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make awesome moments in the history of the Internet and politics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly build a new organization or movement (if it goes well!)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a full time contract position renewed on a monthly basis. Note: since this is a start-up, ongoing funding is not guaranteed, but it&amp;rsquo;s likely we can provide ongoing funding if your work goes well and demonstrates impact.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 16:35:11 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-11T16:35:11Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">151605</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/151605/remote-elasticsearch-and-aws-system-advanced-symbolics?a=OQiR4YQzwdO</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Advanced Symbolics</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>amazon-web-services</category>
      <category>elasticsearch</category>
      <category>security</category>
      <category>sysadmin</category>
      <title>Remote ElasticSearch and AWS System Administration Contract at Advanced Symbolics () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The science behind public opinion polling hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed in 50 years, despite the fact that how people form and share their opinions has changed substantially. &amp;nbsp; There is no longer a need to ask people how they feel &amp;ndash; our Artificial Intelligence&amp;nbsp;can glean it from online content. &amp;nbsp;We work with cutting edge machine learning and text analytics while disrupting how governments and businesses measure their citizens and customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an engineer with experience designing, building and deploying ElasticSearch hosted on AWS to come onboard to examine and improve our current integration. Although this is a short-term contract focused on migrating to a more secure implementation, this system is mission-critical and you will have the chance to make a big impact. There is also the possibility of future work to ensure our installation is maintained properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;This position is remote, but we prefer candidates that have reasonable time-zone overlap with North America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Document how ElasticSearch is used in our code base&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide recommendations as to how we can improve security and performance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Update/migrate our ElasticSearch installation to current stable release&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement improvements after discussion with the team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skills and Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience using ElasticSearch on AWS EC2&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of web security best-practices and how to implement them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Great communication skills in written and verbal English&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with the Ruby and/or R programming languages would be ideal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of the software development life-cycle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Does this sound like you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re self-driven with great time-management skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re resourceful: you figure out what needs to be done, and you find ways to make it happen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a passion for problem solving. Nothing gets you more excited than a tricky problem or a new challenge&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;You enjoy sharing knowledge with and learning from others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We would love to hear more about your experience working with these technologies, and what you think you could bring to this project! We are growing fast right now and hoping to bring on a great candidate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 21:28:46 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-16T21:28:46Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">149133</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/149133/python-developer-web-scraping-scrapinghub?a=O0U3vEcJzIQ</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Scrapinghub</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>scrapy</category>
      <category>scrapy-spider</category>
      <title>Python Developer - Web Scraping at Scrapinghub () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>Scrapinghub is looking for experienced and senior software engineers to join our Professional Services team to work on web crawler development with Scrapy, our flagship open source project.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you interested in building web crawlers harnessing the Scrapinghub platform, which powers crawls of over 3 billion pages a month? Do you like working in a company with a strong open source foundation? Scrapinghub helps companies, ranging from Fortune 500 enterprises to up and coming early stage startups, turn web content into useful data with a cloud-based web crawling platform, off-the-shelf datasets, and turn-key web scraping services.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join us in making the world a better place for web crawler developers with our team of top talented engineers working remotely from more than 30 countries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Role Responsibilities:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, develop and maintain Scrapy web crawlers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leverage the Scrapinghub platform and our open source projects to perform distributed information extraction, retrieval and data processing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify and resolve performance and scalability issues with distributed crawling at scale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help identify, debug and fix problems with open source projects, including Scrapy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scrapinghub&amp;rsquo;s platform and Professional Services offerings have been growing tremendously over the past couple of years but there are a lot of big projects waiting in the pipeline, and in this role you would be a key part of that process. Here&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re looking for:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;About You:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of software development experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid Python knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scrapy experience a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Linux/UNIX, HTTP, HTML, Javascript and Networking.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good communication in written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Availability to work full time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 16:29:01 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-19T16:29:01Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">131735</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/131735/javascript-web-development-bootcamp-mentor-thinkful-inc?a=Ib9hiZ6JVrW</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Thinkful Inc.</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>reactjs</category>
      <category>node.js</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>redux</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <title>JavaScript Web Development Bootcamp Mentor at Thinkful Inc. () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mentor Thinkful's most engaged students as they learn the industry practices and programming skills they need to break into&amp;nbsp;and succeed&amp;nbsp;as a web developer!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our&amp;nbsp;intensive and top rated&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coursereport.com/best-coding-bootcamps&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;(across all 5 categories&lt;/a&gt;)&amp;nbsp;4-6 month web development bootcamp uses the power of one-on-one mentor to mold&amp;nbsp;students into&amp;nbsp;self-sufficient programmers capable of advancing their skills as they grow in their careers for years to come. As a Mentor, you will share best practices with the next generation of developers and teach them&amp;nbsp;how to think like an engineer so that they can&amp;nbsp;continue their growth beyond the program. You will help students master computer science fundamentals while building&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jonwade.codes/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;projects&lt;/a&gt; using full stack JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We've ranked as the number one bootcamp on Course Report &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coursereport.com/best-coding-bootcamps&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;(across all 5 categories&lt;/a&gt;) for over 6 months! Join our incredible community of 320 developers, designers and data scientists laser focused on student success.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thinkful mentors work remotely and set their own hours. The role is a great fit for experts who genuinely love their work and want to share their expertise, experience, and themselves with awesome students and fellow mentors from around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated expertise in using front end technologies at an industry level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced understanding of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Professional Experience with Node.JS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Professional Experience with React.JS and Redux (or willingness to learn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Git and GitHub&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Previous corporate training or teaching experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Great mentors have:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A desire to keep your skills sharp by teaching others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A passion for sharing best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infectious enthusiasm for development and for sharing your craft with others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reflect upon and develop their teaching strategies for each learner&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 14:25:48 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-05T14:25:48Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">133133</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/133133/react-engineer-flux-redux-work-from-home-martiancraft?a=IEdwoFDcy6k</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>MartianCraft</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>reactjs</category>
      <category>redux</category>
      <category>react-redux</category>
      <category>flux</category>
      <category>reactjs-flux</category>
      <title>React Engineer (Flux/Redux) - Work from Home at MartianCraft () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a React&amp;nbsp;Engineer who possesses a passion for pushing technologies to the limits and will work with our team of talented engineers to design and build enterprise apps for Fortune 500 companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are&amp;nbsp;receiving a large number of&amp;nbsp;applications from outside the US. Please take note of the following requirement located at the bottom of the ad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicant MUST be a US Citizen or CURRENTLY be authorized to work in the US to apply for this position. &amp;nbsp;Applicant must reside in the US at time of&amp;nbsp;application and throughout work period. No staffing agencies or recruiters need apply.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and build advanced applications in&amp;nbsp;React&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with outside data sources and API&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work on bug fixing and improving application performance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with clients to collaborate on best practices and approaches&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;REQUIRED SKILLS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years of software development experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of React&amp;nbsp;development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with third-party libraries and APIs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of the general landscape, architectures, trends, and emerging technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding and command of&amp;nbsp;Redux and Flux APIs and Frameworks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PREFERENTIAL SKILLS &amp;amp; EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Past remote work experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Previous small team experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Software consulting or freelancing experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published books and/or blogs&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specific Details&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;US based only, travel to Texas may be required every 2-6 months as required by our client. This is a 40 hour a week contract position. Ready for immediate start on a long term contract.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 18:12:16 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-25T18:12:16Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">148284</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/148284/online-video-instructor-for-devops-testing-linkedin-learning?a=NJfyN5crEZi</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>LinkedIn Learning</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>devops</category>
      <category>continuous-integration</category>
      <category>testing</category>
      <category>unit-testing</category>
      <category>docker</category>
      <title>Online Video Instructor for DevOps &amp; Testing Training at LinkedIn Learning () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Transform people's lives. Teach skills to create opportunity. &amp;nbsp;Apply to be a LinkedIn Learning/Lynda author today!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please note that this is a contract-based course instructor role, not an in-house developer position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Lynda, we believe in connecting people to opportunity by sharing knowledge. With millions of members, your voice and expertise can make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you an experienced technology professional with a passion to teach and share your expertise? Do you thrive on taking the complex and making it simple? 'Is the &quot;why&quot; just as important as the &quot;how&quot; to you? If you have knowledge to share, let&amp;rsquo;s connect! We&amp;rsquo;re seeking devops/SRE professionals and QA/testing engineers to create video training courses for our rapidly-growing audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have a passion for and experience working with the following, let&amp;rsquo;s talk!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;DevOps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;CI/CD tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;TDD/BDD/test automation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infrastructure as Code (Chef/Puppet/Ansible/Terraform)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitoring tools (Nagios, ELK, Sensu, Prometheus)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Site Reliability Engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microservices architecture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud native infrastructure tools: Docker, Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Linkedin Learning/Lynda instructor, you get more than a platform - you get a partner. We pride ourselves on producing the highest quality educational courses available. You&amp;rsquo;ll partner with content area experts to scope and refine your ideas, then work with a professional production team of instructional designers, producers, graphic designers, editors, and QA specialists to assemble your world-class technology training course. Our well-established production process allows you to spend more time creating course content, while we take the lead on designing, producing, and editing the course. Ready to get started?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join our passionate and experienced team of educators and technologists!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note: we are always looking for new authors across the technology spectrum; even if you do not see your technical expertise listed, please inquire and clearly list your topics of expertise/interest.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 15:33:21 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-14T15:33:21Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">131734</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/131734/data-science-bootcamp-mentor-thinkful-inc?a=Ib7ZnszmKRO</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Thinkful Inc.</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>pandas</category>
      <category>machine-learning</category>
      <category>data-science</category>
      <category>numpy</category>
      <title>Data Science Bootcamp Mentor at Thinkful Inc. () (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mentor aspiring Data Scientists enrolled in&amp;nbsp;Thinkful's Data Science Flexible Bootcamp!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The intensive, 4-6 month course helps students become self-sufficient data scientists capable of advancing their skills as they grow in their careers for years to come. As a Mentor, you will meet work one-on-one with your&amp;nbsp;student(s), meeting 3x a week as they build projects and master data science fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thinkful Mentors work remotely and set their own hours. The role is a great fit for experts who genuinely love their work and want to share their expertise, experience, and themselves with awesome students and fellow mentors from around the globe!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Required &amp;nbsp;Experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Python&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Professional Experience as a Data Scientist or in similar role&amp;nbsp;that utilizes modern data science tools and methodologies&amp;nbsp;with a particular focus on machine learning algorithms using packages like scikit-learn or statsmodels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;USA based&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experienced with Panda,&amp;nbsp;NumPy, Matplotlib, Scikit-Learn, Beautiful Soup&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Able to explain&amp;nbsp;mathematical concepts involved in statistics,&amp;nbsp;probability and linear algebra&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Git and GitHub&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A desire to keep your skills sharp by teaching others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;A passion for sharing best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infectious enthusiasm for development and sharing your craft with others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Previous corporate training or teaching experience a plus&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Involvement in local community (i.e. meet-ups) a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 14:18:36 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-05T14:18:36Z</a10:updated>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">146499</guid>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.com/jobs/146499/devops-contractor-guru-mecum-auctions?a=N88pDimlYOY</link>
      <a10:author>
        <a10:name>Mecum Auctions</a10:name>
      </a10:author>
      <category>amazon-web-services</category>
      <category>chef</category>
      <category>continuous-integration</category>
      <category>continuous-delivery</category>
      <category>amazon-ec2</category>
      <title>DevOps Contractor/Guru at Mecum Auctions (Walworth, WI) (allows remote)</title>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The software development team at Mecum Auctions is a small agile group of talented individuals focused on building applications that solve the needs of the business.&amp;nbsp; We are building both internal and customer facing applications focused on enabling our talented staff to do their jobs better or meeting the needs of hundreds of thousands of customers.&amp;nbsp; To enable the software team to grow rapidly, we are looking for an expert to implement scalable production infrastructure and foster infrastructure knowledge within the team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remote candidates are encouraged to apply and all candidates will be hired on a contract basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mecum Auctions does not provide H1B Visa sponsorship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You must reside in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 18:36:15 Z</pubDate>
      <a10:updated>2017-08-20T18:36:15Z</a10:updated>
      <location xmlns="http://stackoverflow.com/jobs/">Walworth, WI</location>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>